Guide to the Book-of-the-Month Club Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Additional Manuscripts (July 2000 Acquisition), circa 1951-1979; Series III; (20 boxes)
  - Jong, Erica. Fruits & vegetables, circa 1971 (Box 56, Folder 813)
  - Josephson, Matthew. Infidel in the temple, circa 1967 (Box 56, Folder 814)
  - Josephson, Matthew and Hannah. Hero of the cities, circa 1969 (Box 57, Folder 815)
    Published under title Al Smith: hero of the cities
  - Kang, Younghill. The grass roof, circa 1966 (Box 57, Folder 816)
  - Kawabata, Yasunari. The master of go, circa 1972 (Box 57, Folder 817)
  - Kennan, George F. (George Frost). Memoirs, 1925-1950, circa 1967 (Box 57, Folder 818)
  - Kinnell, Galway. Flower herding on Mount Monadnock, circa 1964 (Box 57, Folder 819)
  - Kosinksi, Jerzy. Steps, circa 1968 (Box 57, Folder 820)
  - Krause, David, ed. The letters of Sean O'Casey, circa 1975 (Box 57, Folder 821-822)
  - Kuh, Katharine. The open eye: a discerning look at the perplexities of art, circa 1971 (Box 57, Folder 823)
    Published under title The open eye; in pursuit of art
  - Kumin, Maxine. Up country: poems of New England, circa 1972 (Box 57, Folder 824)
  - Lancaster, Osbert. Sailing to Byzantium, circa 1969 (Box 57, Folder 825)
  - Lattimore, Richmond Alexander. The Revelation of John, circa 1962 (Box 57, Folder 826)
  - Lehmann, John. A nest of tigers, circa 1968 (Box 58, Folder 827)
  - Leslie, Cecilie. The golden stairs, circa 1968 (Box 58, Folder 828-829)
  - Lessing, Doris May. Stories, circa 1978 (Box 58, Folder 830)
  - Lewis, C. S. (Clive Staples)
    - Letters to Malcolm: chiefly on prayer, circa 1964 (Box 58, Folder 831)
    - Poems, circa 1965 (Box 58, Folder 832)
  - Linklater, Eric
    - The conquest of England, circa 1966 (Box 58, Folder 833)
    - The survival of Scotland, circa 1968 (Box 58, Folder 834-835)
  - Llewellyn, Richard. Tell me now, and again, circa 1978 (Box 58, Folder 836)
  - Lowell, Robert. Selected Poems, circa 1976 (Box 58, Folder 837)
  - Massie, Robert K. Nicholas and Alexandra, 1967 Jan 24 (Box 59, Folder 838-839)
  - Maugham, Robin. Somerset and all the Maughams, circa 1966 (Box 59, Folder 840)
  - Maugham, W. Somerset (William Somerset). Seventeen lost stories, circa 1969 (Box 59, Folder 841)
  - McAdam, E. L. (Edward Lippincott) and George Milne, eds. Johnson's dictionary: a modern selection, circa 1963 (Box 59, Folder 842)
  - McCarthy, Mary. Birds of America, 1971 May 19 (Box 59, Folder 843)
  - Meredith, William. The wreck of the Thresher and other poems, 1964 Apr (Box 59, Folder 844)
  - Miller, Arthur
    - Incident at Vichy, circa 1965 (Box 59, Folder 845)
    - The price, circa 1968 (Box 59, Folder 846)
    - A view from the bridge, circa 1955 (Box 59, Folder 847)
  - Mishima, Yukio. After the banquet, circa 1963 (Box 59, Folder 848)
  - Moore, Marianne
    - Tell me, tell me: granite, steel, and other topics, circa 1966 (Box 60, Folder 849)
    - "To a giraffe", undated (Box 67, Folder 956)
  - Morley, Christopher. Gentlemen's relish, circa 1955 (Box 60, Folder 850)
  - Morris, Wright. The territory ahead, circa 1958 (Box 60, Folder 851)
  - Murdoch, Iris
    - The nice and the good, circa 1968 (Box 60, Folder 852)
    - The red and the green, circa 1965 (Box 60, Folder 853)
  - Nabokov, Vladimir Vladimirovich
    - The defense, circa 1964 (Box 60, Folder 854)
    - Details of a sunset, circa 1976 (Box 60, Folder 855)
    - Look at the harlequins! (2 copies), circa 1974 (Box 60, Folder 856-857)
    - Mary, circa 1970 (Box 60, Folder 858)
    - Nabokov's congeries, circa 1968 (Box 60, Folder 859)
    - Speak, memory, circa 1966 (Box 60, Folder 860)
    - Transparent things (2 copies), circa 1972 (Box 60, Folder 861-862)
  - Nathan, Robert
    - The fair, circa 1964 (Box 60, Folder 863)
    - Juliet in Mantua, circa 1966 (Box 61, Folder 864)
    - The Mallot diaries, circa 1965 (Box 61, Folder 865)
    - The married man, circa 1962 (Box 61, Folder 866)
    - Stonecliff, circa 1967 (Box 61, Folder 867)
    - The summer meadows, 1973 Oct (Box 61, Folder 868)
  - Nicolson, Nigel, ed. Harold Nicolson: diaries and letters, 1939-1945, v. 2, circa 1967 (Box 61, Folder 869)
  - O'Casey, Sean. Blasts and benedictions, circa 1967 (Box 61, Folder 870)
  - O'Faoláin, Seán. Foreign affairs and other stories (2 copies), circa 1976 (Box 61, Folder 871-872)
  - O'Gorman, Ned. The harvesters' vase, circa 1968 (Box 61, Folder 873)
  - O'Keeffe, Georgia. Georgia O'Keeffe, circa 1976 (Box 61, Folder 874)
  - Oliver, Mary. No voyage and other poems, circa 1965 (Box 61, Folder 875)
  - Omar Khayyam. The Rubaiyyat of Omar Khayaam, circa 1968 (Box 61, Folder 876)
  - Piercy, Marge. Living in the open, circa 1976 (Box 61, Folder 877)
  - Priestley, J.B. (John Boynton)
    - The Edwardians, circa 1970 (Box 61, Folder 878)
    - Essays of five decades, circa 1968 (Box 61, Folder 879)
    - It's an old country, circa 1967 (Box 61, Folder 880)
    - Three novels, circa 1978 (Box 61, Folder 881)
    - Margin released, circa 1962 (Box 61, Folder 882)
    - The Prince of Pleasure and his Regency, circa 1969 (Box 62, Folder 883)
  - Purdy, James
    - Eustace Chisholm, circa 1967 (Box 62, Folder 884)
    - The nephew, circa 1960 (Box 62, Folder 885)
  - Ray, Gordon Norton. "'This ever diverse pair': H.G. Wells and Rebecca West" (2 copies), circa 1974 (Box 62, Folder 886-887)
    Published under title H. G. Wells and Rebecca West
  - Reed, Kit. The better part, circa 1967 (Box 62, Folder 888)
  - Rhys, Jean. Sleep it off, lady, circa 1976 (Box 62, Folder 889)
  - Rich, Adrienne Cecile
    - Diving into the wreck: poems 1971-1972, circa 1973 (Box 62, Folder 890)
    - Necessities of life: poems 1962-1965, circa 1966 (Box 62, Folder 891)
    - Snapshots of a daughter-in-law: poems 1954-1962, circa 1967 (Box 62, Folder 892)
  - Roethke, Theodore. The far field, circa 1964 (Box 62, Folder 893)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel
    - Breaking open, circa 1974 (Box 62, Folder 894)
    - The gates, circa 1976 (Box 62, Folder 895)
    - The orgy, circa 1965 (Box 62, Folder 896)
    - The speed of darkness, circa 1968 (Box 62, Folder 897)
  - Sackville-West, V. (Victoria). A joy of gardening, circa 1977 (Box 62, Folder 898)
  - Sarton, May
    - A grain of mustard seed, circa 1971 (Box 62, Folder 899)
    - A world of light, 1976 May 11 (Box 62, Folder 900)
  - Schuyler, James. Hymn to life, circa 1974 (Box 62, Folder 901)
  - Sexton, Anne
    - All my pretty ones, circa 1962 (Box 62, Folder 902)
    - The book of folly, circa 1972 (Box 62, Folder 903)
    - The death notebooks, circa 1974 (Box 62, Folder 904)
    - Live or die, circa 1966 (Box 62, Folder 905)
    - Love poems, circa 1969 (Box 62, Folder 906)
  - Sillitoe, Alan. The widower's son, circa 1977 (Box 62, Folder 907)
  - Simpson, Louis. Selected Poems, circa 1965 (Box 62, Folder 908)
  - Sitwell, Edith, Dame. Taken care of, circa 1965 (Box 63, Folder 909)
  - Smith, William Jay. The tin can and other poems, circa 1966 (Box 63, Folder 910)
  - Snodgrass, W. D. (William De Witt). After experience, circa 1968 (Box 63, Folder 911)
  - Snow, C. P. (Charles Percy). In their wisdom, circa 1974 (Box 63, Folder 912)
  - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr Isaevich
    - The first circle, circa 1968 (Box 63, Folder 913-915)
    - The Gulag Archipelago, circa 1978 (Box 63, Folder 916)
  - Spark, Muriel
    - The girls of slender means, circa 1963 (Box 63, Folder 917)
    - The public image, circa 1968 (Box 63, Folder 918)
    - Territorial rights, circa 1979 (Box 63, Folder 919)
  - Spender, Stephen
    - D.H. Lawrence: novelist, poet, prophet, circa 1973 (Box 63, Folder 920)
    - Love-hate relations, circa 1974 (Box 64, Folder 921)
    - Selected poems, circa 1964 (Box 64, Folder 922)
    - The thirties and after, 1978 Jun 23 (Box 64, Folder 923)
  - Stanford, Ann. In Mediterranean air, circa 1977 (Box 64, Folder 924)
  - Steegmuller, Francis, ed.. "Your Isadora". The Love Story of Isadora Duncan and Gordon Craig, circa 1974 (Box 64, Folder 925)
  - Sullivan, A. M. (Aloysius Michael). Selected lyrics and sonnets, circa 1970 (Box 64, Folder 926)
  - Tolkien, J. R. R. (John Ronald Reuel). The Silmarillion, circa 1977 (Box 64, Folder 927)
  - Wain, John. The pardoners tale, circa 1978 (Box 64, Folder 928)
  - Wakoski, Diane. Inside the blood factory, circa 1968 (Box 64, Folder 929)
  - Walker, Alice
    - Once, circa 1968 (Box 64, Folder 930)
    - Revolutionary petunias, circa 1973 (Box 64, Folder 931)
  - Warren, Robert Penn
    - Flood, circa 1963 (Box 64, Folder 932)
    - Homage to Theodore Dreiser, circa 1971 (Box 64, Folder 933)
    - Incarnations, circa 1968 (Box 64, Folder 934)
    - Meet me in the green glen (2 copies), circa 1971 (Box 64, Folder 935-936)
    - Selected poems: new and old 1923-1966, circa 1966 (Box 64, Folder 937)
    - Selected poems 1923-1975, 1976 Feb 27 (Box 64, Folder 938)
    - Who speaks for the Negro? (2 copies), circa 1965 (Box 65, Folder 939-940)
    - You, emperors, and others, circa 1960 (Box 65, Folder 941)
  - Wegner, Robert E. The poetry and prose of E.E. Cummings, circa 1965 (Box 65, Folder 942)
  - Whitbread, Thomas B. (Thomas Bacon). Four infinitives, circa 1964 (Box 65, Folder 943)
  - White, Patrick
    - The burnt ones, circa 1964 (Box 65, Folder 944)
    - The cockatoos, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 955)
    - The solid mandala, circa 1966 (Box 65, Folder 945)
  - Wilbur, Richard. Walking to sleep, circa 1969 (Box 66, Folder 946)
  - Wilder, Thornton. The cabala; and The woman of Andros, circa 1968 (Box 66, Folder 947)
  - Wilson, Edmund
    - The devils and Canon Barham, 1973 Mar 1 (Box 66, Folder 948)
    - Upstate, circa 1971 (Box 66, Folder 949)
  - Wodehouse, P. G. (Pelham Grenville)
    - Biffen's millions, circa 1964 (Box 66, Folder 950)
    - Code of the Woosters, circa 1969 (Box 66, Folder 951)
    - Jeeves and the tie that binds, 1971 May 5 (Box 66, Folder 952)
  - Woiwode, Larry. Even tide, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 953)